A Guide to the Annual Tax and Operation Reports for Railroads, 1899-1975
Library of Virginia
- Series I. Annual Tax and Operation Reports for Railroads, 1899-1975., Extent: 366 boxes; 165 cubic feet. (Box 1-366)
  - 1966.
    - Carolina, Clinchfield, and Ohio, 1966 (Box 344)
    - Carolina and Northwestern (2 folders), 1966 (Box 344)
    - Chesapeake and Ohio, 1966 (Box 344)
    - Chesapeake Western, 1966 (Box 344)
    - Clinchfield, 1966 (Box 344)
    - Interstate, 1966 (Box 344)
    - Louisville and Nashville, 1966 (Box 344)
    - Norfolk, Franklin, and Danville, 1966 (Box 344)
    - Norfolk and Portsmouth Belt Line, 1966 (Box 344)
    - Norfolk and Western, 1966 (Box 344)
    - Norfolk Southern, 1966 (Box 345)
    - Pennsylvania, 1966 (Box 345)
    - Railway Express Agency Incorporated, 1966 (Box 345)
    - Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac, 1966 (Box 345)
    - Richmond Terminal, 1966 (Box 345)
    - Rosslyn Connecting, 1966 (Box 345)
    - Seaboard Air Line, 1966 (Box 345)
    - Southern, 1966 (Box 345)
    - Virginia and Southwestern, 1966 (Box 345)
    - Virginia Blue Ridge, 1966 (Box 345)
    - Virginia Central, 1966 (Box 345)
    - Washington and Old Dominion, 1966 (Box 345)
    - Winchester and Potomac, 1966 (Box 346)
    - Winchester and Strasburg, 1966 (Box 346)
    - Winchester and Western, 1966 (Box 346)
  - 1967.
    - Carolina, Clinchfield, and Ohio, 1967 (Box 346)
    - Carolina and Northwestern, 1967 (Box 346)
    - Chesapeake and Ohio, 1967 (Box 346)
    - Chesapeake Western, 1967 (Box 346)
    - Clinchfield, 1967 (Box 346)
    - Danville and Western, 1967 (Box 346)
    - Interstate, 1967 (Box 346)
    - Louisville and Nashville, 1967 (Box 346)
    - Norfolk, Franklin, and Danville, 1967 (Box 346)
    - Norfolk and Portsmouth Belt Line, 1967 (Box 346)
    - Norfolk and Western, 1967 (Box 346)
    - Norfolk Southern, 1967 (Box 347)
    - Pennsylvania, 1967 (Box 347)
    - Railway Express Agency Incorporated (2 folders), 1967 (Box 347)
    - Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac, 1967 (Box 347)
    - Richmond Terminal, 1967 (Box 347)
    - Rosslyn Connecting, 1967 (Box 347)
    - Seaboard Coast Line, 1967 (Box 347)
    - Southern, 1967 (Box 347)
    - Virginia and Southwestern, 1967 (Box 347)
    - Virginia Blue Ridge, 1967 (Box 347)
    - Winchester and Potomac, 1967 (Box 348)
    - Winchester and Strasburg, 1967 (Box 348)
    - Winchester and Western, 1967 (Box 348)
  - 1968.
    - Baltimore and Ohio, 1968 (Box 348)
    - Carolina, Clinchfield, and Ohio, 1968 (Box 348)
    - Carolina and Northwestern, 1968 (Box 348)
    - Chesapeake and Ohio, 1968 (Box 348)
    - Chesapeake Western, 1968 (Box 348)
    - Clinchfield, 1968 (Box 348)
    - Danville and Western, 1968 (Box 348)
    - Interstate, 1968 (Box 348)
    - Louisville and Nashvile, 1968 (Box 348)
    - Norfolk, Franklin, and Danville, 1968 (Box 348)
    - Norfolk and Portmouth Belt Line, 1968 (Box 349)
    - Norfolk and Western, 1968 (Box 349)
    - Norfolk Southern, 1968 (Box 349)
    - Penn Central Transportation Company, 1968 (Box 349)
    - Railway Express Agency Incorporated, 1968 (Box 349)
    - Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac, 1968 (Box 349)
    - Richmond Terminal, 1968 (Box 349)
    - Rosslyn Connecting, 1968 (Box 349)
    - Seaboard Coastline, 1968 (Box 349)
    - Southern, 1968 (Box 349)
    - Virginia and Southwestern, 1968 (Box 349)
    - Virginia Blue Ridge, 1968 (Box 350)
    - Washington and Old Dominion, 1968 (Box 350)
    - Winchester and Potomac, 1968 (Box 350)
    - Winchester and Strasburg, 1968 (Box 350)
    - Winchester and Western, 1968 (Box 350)
  - 1969.
    - Baltimore and Ohio, 1969 (Box 350)
    - Carolina, Clinchfield, and Ohio, 1969 (Box 350)
    - Carolina and Northwestern, 1969 (Box 350)
    - Chesapeake and Ohio, 1969 (Box 350)
    - Chesapeake Western, 1969 (Box 350)
    - Clinchfield, 1969 (Box 350)
    - Danville and Western, 1969 (Box 350)
    - Haysi, 1969 (Box 350)
    - Interstate, 1969 (Box 350)
    - Louisville and Nashville, 1969 (Box 350)
    - Norfolk, Franklin, and Danville, 1969 (Box 351)
    - Norfolk and Portsmouth Belt Line, 1969 (Box 351)
    - Norfolk and Western, 1969 (Box 351)
    - Norfolk Southern, 1969 (Box 351)
    - Penn Central Transportation Company, 1969 (Box 351)
    - Railway Express Agency Incorporated, 1969 (Box 351)
    - Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac, 1969 (Box 351)
    - Richmond Terminal, 1969 (Box 351)
    - Seaboard Coast Line, 1969 (Box 351)
    - Southern, 1969 (Box 351)
    - Virginia and Southwestern, 1969 (Box 351)
    - Virginia and Southwestern, 1969 (Box 352)
    - Virginia Blue Ridge, 1969 (Box 352)
    - Winchester and Potomac, 1969 (Box 352)
    - Winchester and Strasburg, 1969 (Box 352)
    - Winchester and Western, 1969 (Box 352)
  - 1970.
    - Baltimore and Ohio, 1970 (Box 352)
    - Carolina, Clinchfield, and Ohio, 1970 (Box 352)
    - Carolina and Northwestern, 1970 (Box 352)
    - Chesapeake and Ohio, 1970 (Box 352)
    - Chesapeake Western, 1970 (Box 352)
    - Clinchfield, 1970 (Box 352)
    - Danville and Western, 1970 (Box 352)
    - Haysi, 1970 (Box 352)
    - Interstate, 1970 (Box 352)
    - Louisville and Nashville, 1970 (Box 353)
    - Norfolk, Franklin, and Danville, 1970 (Box 353)
    - Norfolk and Portsmouth Belt Line, 1970 (Box 353)
    - Norfolk and Western, 1970 (Box 353)
    - Norfolk Southern, 1970 (Box 353)
    - Penn Central Transportation Company, 1970 (Box 353)
    - Railway Express Agency Incorporated, 1970 (Box 353)
    - Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac, 1970 (Box 353)
    - Richmond Terminal, 1970 (Box 353)
    - Seaboard Coast Line, 1970 (Box 353)
    - Southern, 1970 (Box 354)
    - Virginia and Southwestern, 1970 (Box 354)
    - Virginia Blue Ridge, 1970 (Box 354)
    - Winchester and Potomac, 1970 (Box 354)
    - Winchester and Strasburg, 1970 (Box 354)
    - Winchester and Western, 1970 (Box 354)
  - 1971.
    - Auto Train Corporation, 1971 (Box 354)
    - Baltimore and Ohio, 1971 (Box 354)
    - Carolina, Clinchfield, and Ohio, 1971 (Box 354)
    - Carolina and Northwestern, 1971 (Box 354)
    - Chesapeake and Ohio, 1971 (Box 354)
    - Chesapeake Western, 1971 (Box 354)
    - Clinchfield, 1971 (Box 355)
    - Danville and Western, 1971 (Box 355)
    - Haysi, 1971 (Box 355)
    - Interstate, 1971 (Box 355)
    - Louisville and Nashville, 1971 (Box 355)
    - National, 1971 (Box 355)
    - Norfolk, Franklin, and Danville, 1971 (Box 355)
    - Norfolk and Portsmouth Belt Line, 1971 (Box 355)
    - Norfolk and Western, 1971 (Box 355)
    - Norfolk Southern, 1971 (Box 355)
    - Penn Central Transportation Corporation, 1971 (Box 355)
    - Railway Express Agency Incorporated, 1971 (Box 356)
    - Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac, 1971 (Box 356)
    - Richmond Terminal, 1971 (Box 356)
    - Seaboard Coast Line, 1971 (Box 356)
    - Southern, 1971 (Box 356)
    - Virginia and Southwestern, 1971 (Box 356)
    - Virginia Blue Ridge, 1971 (Box 356)
    - Winchester and Potomac, 1971 (Box 356)
    - Winchester and Strasburg, 1971 (Box 356)
    - Winchester and Western, 1971 (Box 356)
  - 1972.
    - Auto Train Corporation, 1972 (Box 356)
    - Baltimore and Ohio, 1972 (Box 356)
    - Carolina, Clinchfield, and Ohio, 1972 (Box 356)
    - Carolina and Northwestern, 1972 (Box 356)
    - Chesapeake and Ohio, 1972 (Box 357)
    - Chesapeake Western, 1972 (Box 357)
    - Clinchfield, 1972 (Box 357)
    - Haysi, 1972 (Box 357)
    - Interstate, 1972 (Box 357)
    - Louisville and Nashville, 1972 (Box 357)
    - National, 1972 (Box 357)
    - Norfolk, Franklin, and Danville, 1972 (Box 357)
    - Norfolk and Portsmouth Belt Line, 1972 (Box 357)
    - Norfolk and Western, 1972 (Box 357)
    - Norfolk Southern, 1972 (Box 358)
    - Penn Central Transportation Company, 1972 (Box 358)
    - Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac, 1972 (Box 358)
    - Richmond Terminal, 1972 (Box 358)
    - Seaboard Coast Line, 1972 (Box 358)
    - Southern, 1972 (Box 358)
    - Virginia and Southwestern, 1972 (Box 358)
    - Virginia Blue Ridge, 1972 (Box 358)
    - Winchester and Potomac, 1972 (Box 358)
    - Winchester and Strasburg, 1972 (Box 358)
    - Winchester and Western, 1972 (Box 358)
  - 1973.
    - Auto Train Corporation, 1973 (Box 359)
    - Baltimore and Ohio, 1973 (Box 359)
    - Carolina, Clinchfield, and Ohio, 1973 (Box 359)
    - Carolina and Northwestern, 1973 (Box 359)
    - Chesapeake and Ohio, 1973 (Box 359)
    - Chesapeake Western, 1973 (Box 359)
    - Clinchfield, 1973 (Box 359)
    - Danville and Western, 1973 (Box 359)
    - Haysi, 1973 (Box 359)
    - Interstate, 1973 (Box 359)
    - Louisville and Nashville, 1973 (Box 359)
    - Norfolk, Franklin, and Danville, 1973 (Box 360)
    - Norfolk and Portsmouth Belt Line, 1973 (Box 360)
    - Norfolk and Western, 1973 (Box 360)
    - Norfolk Southern, 1973 (Box 360)
    - Penn Central Transportation Company, 1973 (Box 360)
    - Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac, 1973 (Box 360)
    - Richmond Terminal, 1973 (Box 360)
    - Seaboard Coast Line, 1973 (Box 360)
    - Southern, 1973 (Box 360)
    - Virginia and Southwestern, 1973 (Box 360)
    - Virginia Blue Ridge, 1973 (Box 360)
    - Winchester and Potomac, 1973 (Box 361)
    - Winchester and Strasburg, 1973 (Box 361)
    - Winchester and Western, 1973 (Box 361)
  - 1974.
    - Auto Train Corporation, 1974 (Box 361)
    - Baltimore and Ohio, 1974 (Box 361)
    - Chesapeake Western, 1974 (Box 361)
    - Clinchfield, 1974 (Box 361)
    - Danville and Western, 1974 (Box 361)
    - Haysi, 1974 (Box 361)
    - Interstate, 1974 (Box 361)
    - Louisville and Nashville, 1974 (Box 361)
    - National, 1974 (Box 362)
    - Norfolk, Franklin, and Danville, 1974 (Box 362)
    - Norfolk and Portsmouth Belt Line, 1974 (Box 362)
    - Norfolk and Western, 1974 (Box 362)
    - Norfolk Southern, 1974 (Box 362)
    - Penn Central Transportation Company, 1974 (Box 362)
    - Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac, 1974 (Box 362)
    - Richmond Terminal, 1974 (Box 362)
    - Seaboard Coast Line, 1974 (Box 362)
    - Southern, 1974 (Box 362)
    - Virginia and Southwestern, 1974 (Box 363)
    - Virginia Blue Ridge, 1974 (Box 363)
    - Virginia Central, 1974 (Box 363)
    - Winchester and Potomac, 1974 (Box 363)
    - Winchester and Strasburg, 1974 (Box 363)
    - Winchester and Western, 1974 (Box 363)
  - 1975.
    - Auto Train Corporation, 1975 (Box 363)
    - Baltimore and Ohio, 1975 (Box 363)
    - Carolina, Clinchfield, and Ohio, 1975 (Box 363)
    - Chesapeake and Ohio, 1975 (Box 363)
    - Chesapeake Western, 1975 (Box 363)
    - Clinchfield (2 folders), 1975 (Box 363)
    - Danville and Western, 1975 (Box 364)
    - Haysi, 1975 (Box 364)
    - Interstate, 1975 (Box 364)
    - Louisville and Nashville, 1975 (Box 364)
    - National, 1975 (Box 364)
    - Norfolk, Franklin, and Danville, 1975 (Box 364)
    - Norfolk and Portsmouth Belt Line, 1975 (Box 364)
    - Norfolk and Western, 1975 (Box 364)
    - Norfolk Southern, 1975 (Box 364)
    - Penn Central Transportation Company, 1975 (Box 364)
    - Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac, 1975 (Box 365)
    - Richmond Terminal, 1975 (Box 365)
    - Seaboard Coast Line, 1975 (Box 365)
    - Southern, 1975 (Box 365)
    - Virginia and Southwest, 1975 (Box 365)
    - Virginia Blue Ridge, 1975 (Box 365)
    - Winchester and Potomac, 1975 (Box 365)
    - Winchester and Stasburg, 1975 (Box 365)
    - Winchester and Western, 1975 (Box 365)